k1speed.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy | K1 Speed

At K1 Speed, privacy of individual visitor data is of primary importance. We work diligently to protect confidentiality, restrict transfer of personal data, incorporate technical safeguards and appropriate security policies, and identify privacy implications in new services. We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us.

##### What This privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we may collect when you are on the web site, and when you use our site services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.

##### Information Collected

At K1 Speed, your privacy and the protection of your data is our main concern. Collecting the information, how the information is used, with whom the information is shared. The kind of security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under K1 Speed control, How to correct any inaccuracies in the information. If you feel that our company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, please contact us.The information collected and used. K1 Speed is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way that varies from what is disclosed in this statement. K1 Speed collects information from our users at several different areas on our site. You may receive information regarding new features, services and special offers we think you’ll find valuable. Registration is required in order to use this website, and a user must create an account prior to completing any purchase. Users are required to provide their name, email address, zip code, phone number and a password of 5-16 characters in length. This information is necessary in order for us to contact users about services on our site for which they have expressed interest and so that you may later login to our site to check your order status and account history. K1 Speed order forms request data from users including: Contact information such as name and shipping address; financial information such as credit card number, expiration date, billing address, and billing phone number. This information is used for billing purposes to verify that the customer and to fill customers’ orders. If we encounter difficulty when processing an order, this contact information is used to contact the user. This information is collected from a secure web page and encrypted for our customers’ protection. It is not sold to anyone else under any circumstances. We may disclose this information to your credit card issuing bank if a fraudulent order is being investigated or disputed by you.

##### Cookies

Cookies are data stored on the end-user’s hard drive with information that relates directly to the end-user’s visit to our web site. Any information placed in the cookie is accessible only to K1 Speed, and will not be sold or shared with anyone else under any circumstances. We use a cookie to store a unique session identifier, which allows us to maintain shopping cart and web site selections from one page request to the next, and maintain session information from one visit to the next. By setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in more than once, thereby saving time while visiting our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still browse our site. However, the user experience will be greatly curtailed. In addition, the user will be unable to log in or make a purchase. Cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance users’ experience and display products that relate directly to individual user preferences. Some of our business partners and/or advertisers may also use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

##### AdRoll

As you browse k1speed.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what your interests are. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with K1 Speed. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can [visit this page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

##### Sharing

We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We value your privacy at K1 Speed, and will never release any account information to anyone outside of the necessary core groups that help our business function unless our customers give us the authority to do so.

##### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

##### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that K1 Speed is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

##### E-Mail

If a user wishes to subscribe to our emails we ask for contact information such as name and email address. If at any time you should wish to unsubscribe, please send an email to our customer service group with your request and the e-mail address you used to create your account.If you feel that your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact [TRUSTe](https://www.trustarc.com/consumer-resources/), an independent privacy organization.
